corrections = {
    "UT Austin Invitational 18-19, #22": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "25",
        "explanation": "Takes abt 1 hour to climb ->  ~500 kcal burned, 1 mol ATP = 7.3 kcal\n500/7.3 * 6E23 = 4e25 molecules",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #5": {
        "question": "What is 2^12?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #25": {
        "question": "What is the probability of a randomly selected person on Earth having an IQ of above 200?",
        "answer": "-11",
        "explanation": "normCdf with mean as 100 and SD as 15 gives 1.32e-11",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 17-18, #19": {
        "question": "[Question #6: Yo mamma so fat, she took all the Big Macs sold in the US last year and gobbled \u2019em right up! How many pounds of fat are in yo mamma now? Assume that yo mama ain\u2019t burning any o\u2019 those calories, cuz ain\u2019t nobody got time for that!]\n\nYo mamma not only fat, she so fat that she is seriously concerned about her health and well-being. How many hours would she have to run in order to burn off all those delicious Big Macs from question 6?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #25": {
        "question": "How many seconds would it take the average nuclear plant to generate the amount of energy found in the question above? (Question above: How much energy has been used through the consumption of gasoline by all the cars in the world since the invention of the automobile?)",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #6": {
        "question": "What is 10 ^ (3log(5) + log(20) + 2log(2)) ? Here log denotes the base 10 logarithm.",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #15": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "Average person drinks about 2 liters of water a day. 2 liters/day * 365 days/year * 80 years = 58400 liters.",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #43": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "Pew Research Center says it is 22 million people in 2023. Census.gov says that it was 27.6\nmillion people in 2021. It will likely not be 50+ million in 2023",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #13": {
        "question": "How many calories do I burn if I climb the Great Wall one stair at a time?",
        "answer": "3",
        "explanation": "3100 stairs on the Great Wall of China. 1 stair burns 0.17 calories. 3100 *.17 = 527 calories",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #6": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "63 games with 2 possible winners each. 63 * log(2) = 18.96",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #18 [2018 Brown Q19]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "0",
        "explanation": "Height of Washington Monument is 169.29 m. Thickness of a quarter is 1.75 mm and its mass is 6 g. 169.29 m * 1 quarter / .00175 m * 6 grams / 1 quarter * 1 metric ton / E6 grams = .58 metric tons or about 1 metric ton.",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #75 [2019 Polytechnic Q19]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "According to avma.org in 2018, there were 76,811,305 dogs as pets.",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #1": {
        "question": "What is 2^2017?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #11 [2019 Eastside / Haslett Q14]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "Lots of sources saying 30-40 trillion or around 37 trillion",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "What is (1/7)^35?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2019 LISO Q14]": {
        "question": "Your airplane masses 8 grams. How many fully loaded Airbus A380s is that?",
        "answer": "-8",
        "explanation": "fully loaded airbus is ~1e6 lbs or ~5e8 lbs, answer is 8/(5e8) or approx -8",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #15": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Molar_ionization_energies_of_the_elements\n\nnot specified which ionization energy but definitely not 9995",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #66 [2019 Northmont Q5]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-32",
        "explanation": "jupiter is more massive than a housefly",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "earth to moon: 3.8e8 meters\npenny thickness: 1.52e-3 meters\nanswer: 2.5e11 pennies",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #7": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-1",
        "explanation": "Speed of a bullet is 180-1500 m/s. It does not take 10^11 seconds for a bullet to travel 100 meters.",
        "credit": "Hudson Tien (hsin_tn)"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 22-23, #33": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "sun to earth = 1.5e11 m\nSR 71 blackbird top speed = 9.8e2 m/s\n= e8 seconds",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #22": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "US debt is 32.7 trillion, US GDP is around 25 trillion. 32.7 - 25 trillion = 7.7 trillion",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #34": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1930",
        "explanation": "2023 * log(9) = 1930",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #16": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-10",
        "explanation": "3934km = e-10 parsecs",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #26": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "not sure what the right answer is but it's definitely not -29",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 18-19, #13": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "10^15 m/s is superluminal, answer should be 8 since c is 3x10^8 m/s, neutron would have to be moving very close to that",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-4",
        "explanation": "A fermi test is 50 minutes; 50 min/test * hr/60 min * day/24 hrs * year / 365 days = .0001 years/test or 10E-4",
        "credit": "Elytraflight, Milpitas Scioly"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 22-23, #1": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "0",
        "explanation": "There are 365 episodes of Teletubbies according to Google, hence 1 episode per day should last 1 year (10^0)",
        "credit": "Elytraflight, MHS Scioly"
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #16": {
        "question": "Such a computer: (An Intel i7 chip if all CMOS transistors were replaced with BJTs on an infinite breadboard, assuming that all holes on the breadboard are filled and used solely for the BJT pins.)",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #11": {
        "question": "Suppose that Feliks Zemdegs (a speedcuber from Australia) takes 10 seconds to solve every Rubik's cube. How long would it take him, in years, to solve the number of cubes found in the question above? [Number of cubes = total arrangements of rubiks cubes]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "This question should not be included as it references a previous question, which is not displayed.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #18": {
        "question": "How many dislikes does this same video (the most viewed video) have?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #16 [2018 Harvard Q4]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "Google how many red blood cells are in the human body? and the answer is 2.4 million cells per second times by 60 to change it to minute and you get 144 million cells per minute.",
        "credit": "Staplers"
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "the 100k is per household, it is likely much lower when accounting every single citizen",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #37": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-8",
        "explanation": "Red light wavelength is about 650nm (6.5E-7 m). Length of a football field (including endzones) is about 110m. 6.5E-7 / 110 = 5.9E-9. Thus, Fermi answer is (-8)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #45": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-6",
        "explanation": "Red light wavelength is about 650 nm = 6.5E-7m = Fermi answer (-6)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #39": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "35 trillion red blood cells in human body, see source: https://www.texasheart.org/heart-health/heart-information-center/topics/blood-cells/#:~:text=Red%20blood%20cells%20carry%20oxygen,span%20of%20about%20120%20days.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 22-23, #17": {
        "question": "Total hours of television watched in the US every day.",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "The average person in the us could watch 1.5 hours (500,000,000/331,900,000) to 15 hours (4,999,999,999/331,900,000) and it would fall under 10^9 (1,000,000,000) hours total.",
        "credit": "sharp59#6969"
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #31": {
        "question": "They say that it took Thomas Edison 1,000 tries to successfully create the first lightbulb. How many Navajo Indians died in that amount of time?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #10": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "6.3% is above 5, which means the Fermi answer should be 1",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #12": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "The height of mount Everest is 8849.9 meters which when converted to nanometers is 10^13.",
        "credit": "BossCrusher667"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #98 [2019 ATX Regionals Q41]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "The area of the USA is around 10 million km^2 which is 10^7",
        "credit": "BossCrusher667"
    },
    "University of Michigan Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "avocados grow at 2.5 ft/year, takes 100 years to grow 300 ft. so 10^4 days",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #32": {
        "question": "Suppose you play a game with the following rules: you roll a fair 20 sided die five times and flip a fair coin. If you roll a twenty every time and get heads, then you win $1,000,000,000. You must pay $20 to play the game. How much money do you expect to win from playing the game 1,000,000 times?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2019 WWPN Q3]": {
        "question": "If I had a nickel for every time an American driver was pulled over for speeding, how many years would it take for me to become the richest person in the world?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "The richest person has 280 billion net worth. That means you need 56 billion nickels and the average is 41 million people an year. I think this question might be old",
        "credit": "lordofthesnowleopards (discord)"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #32": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "in nanometers, 380 nanometers becomes 2 for fermi",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #1": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "When you put 2^32 in a calculator, you get 4294967296 which is 4.2*10^9 so the answer is 9",
        "credit": "BTHS Science Olympiad"
    },
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #25": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "The ISS has an orbital velocity of ~7000 m/s",
        "credit": "trainboi01"
    },
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #15": {
        "question": "Determine the number of barns [Barn = 1.00 * 10 -28 m2 ] covered by Washington state\u2019s apple orchards.",
        "answer": "if you dont change it then the answer is technically 0 since 00*10^-28 is 0",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (randomsci) 22-23, #23": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "24",
        "explanation": "It's asking for the moles of the water in the mol of moles, a mol of moles has 6.02x10^23 moles in it, so thats how many moles of water are in it. For the answer to be 48 it would have to be asking for the molecules of water.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #3": {
        "question": "0.1^89",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "1^89 is 1... which happens to be a fermi answer of 0.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #40": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "molar mass of benzene is 78.11g which is 7.8e7 micrograms, making the answer 8 not 7 since you round up.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #67 [2018 WWPN Tryouts Q1]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "25",
        "explanation": "24 in each mol, i doubt you have over 100 mols in a cup of water cause that would be a kilogram",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 17-18, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "23",
        "explanation": "There are 1.335x10^21 liters of water in the oceans, and since there are about 200 teaspoons in a liter, the answer should be 2x10^23->23.",
        "credit": "emptiespace on disc"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #85 [2018 U Georgia Q2]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "3",
        "explanation": "Google (i think the first result is right)",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #16": {
        "question": "Using just the letters in the alphabet, how many unique 26-letter sequences are possible?",
        "answer": "37",
        "explanation": "Gm...\n\nit is 26 to power 26... equal 6156119580207157310796674288400203776..\n\nmethinks answer thus 37..\n\nRB",
        "credit": "Craig buszka"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #131 [2019 New Trier Q10]": {
        "question": "How many licks to the center of a tootsie pop?",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "Google and nigahiga",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #5": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-1",
        "explanation": "The answer is requested in kg. The weight is 174g and is about 10^-1 in kg.",
        "credit": "uknow4546"
    },
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #14": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "15",
        "explanation": "6.7*10^14 is the exact answer and would be 15 in Fermi.",
        "credit": "uknow4546"
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #36": {
        "question": "What percentage is that volume compared to mL of water on Earth? [That volume: mL of blood does our heart pumps each day]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #60": {
        "question": "The Ackermann function is defined by \n\u2022 A(0, n) = n + 1 \u2022 A(m, 0) = A(m \u2212 1, 1)\n\u2022 A(m, n) = A(m \u2212 1; A(m, n \u2212 1)) \nSome values include: A(2, 3) = 9 and A(4, 1) = 65533\nWhat is A(4, 2)? [SI/2017 USD]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #25": {
        "question": "The current meerkat population is about 500,000 Approximately how many of these meerkats will be murdered by their own species if we follow all of them to their cause of death? Hint: Meerkats have been deemed the \"most murderous\" mammal species.",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "BTHS SciOly"
    },
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #27": {
        "question": "43^29",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "It looks like they meant 43^29 since the answer would be 47",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #6": {
        "question": "How tall is Mount Everest (in meters)?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #1": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "A study in the journal Earth Surface Processes and Landforms, written by Dr. Robert A. Morton of the U.S. Geological Survey, predicted that there are 7.5*10^18 grains of sand on earth. Based off other sources this is also the accepted number in academia.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #33 [2018 Westlake Q47]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-21",
        "explanation": "Diameter of a helium atom is 9.8*10^-11 meters and the diameter of the sun is 1.3927 * 10^9 meters.  Dividing this gives us 7.0366913*10^-20 which is -21 in fermi units.",
        "credit": "BTHS Science Olympiad!!"
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #33": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "238,900 miles to the moon * 1 hour / 3 miles (average walking pace) * 60 mins / 1 hr * 60 sec / 1 min = 286,680,000 seconds, or 2.8 * 10^8, answer is 8",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #10": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-7",
        "explanation": "calculate it yourself",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #31": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "Maybe people got less interested in making soup or something, but 300 million->8 results show up if you look it up on a standard school laptop.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #7": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "21",
        "explanation": "Gm...\nSurface area of Moon is 3.8 10^13 m^2...\nso Volume of Glass.. is.. 1.9 * 10^12 m^3 OR 1.9 * 10^18 cm^3\nTHUS... around 4 * 10^18 gram or 4 * 10^21 milligram\n\nRB",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #110 [2019 Monta Vista Q22]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "The US GDP is 2*10^13 USD and the average cost of a car is 3.5*10^4 USD.  When you divide these 2 you get 6.5*10^8 and then you round up to get 10^9",
        "credit": "BTHS SciOly"
    },
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #15": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "There are 30 galaxies in our local group. The logarithm of 30 is approximately 1.477 which would be rounded down to one.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #12": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "Google says that the Atlantic is 4.9 million meters, and that a snail speed is 0.01 meters per second. This gives 4900000/0.01->8 as the fermi answer.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (randomsci) 22-23, #27": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "78",
        "explanation": "The Google Calculator says 6x10^77 -> 78 for the fermi answer.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 22-23, #38": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "Google says that it takes 820 hours to walk to the end of a minecraft world. Multiply this by 60 to get 49200. This gets pretty close to the 5 midpoint, but does round down to 4.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #49": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "Simply divided the thickness of the average piece of paper by the wavelength of blue light",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #22": {
        "question": "Evaluate (\u03c0e)^(\u03c0e)",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #19": {
        "question": "It's Chris's birthday! How many times should he roll a fair 10^10000-sided die before expecting to see a number twice (not necessarily consecutively) ?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #11": {
        "question": "What is the sum of the numbers from 1 to 10^5 ?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Sum of numbers 1-105 is 5,565, or 4.",
        "credit": "Asher N"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #7": {
        "question": "On a chess board, suppose that the queens must be arranged in a manner such that none of the queens could capture another (i.e. none of the queens can be under attack). How many such configurations are possible? Do not include boards that are reflections, rotations, etc.",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "This helps to clarify what the question is about. It was kind of \"cut off\" in the beginning.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #41": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "This is an interest question, to solve this you do 1500*(1.05)^85 which results in approximately 950,00, if continuously compounded it would be about 105,000, both of which are rounded to 100,000 which in fermi notation is 5",
        "credit": "iampotatoz"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #6 [2019 Virginia Tech Q4]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "22",
        "explanation": "Volume of Pacific Ocean is 5E+17m^3, roughly 1e+4 sheets of paper fit in a cubic meter. Should be 21 or 22.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #22 [2018 Acton-Box Q15]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "Searched it up on google. It is around 20 million (10^7)",
        "credit": "Purple"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #46": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Google says it's ~5700 years, which is fermi 4 (original answer fermi 11)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #1": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "The mass of the sun and the solar mass is around the same, where did 6 come from",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #80 [2019 U Chicago Q21]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "I have been listening to Gucci Gang since 1776 and I can confirm this answer is right",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #109 [2018 U Florida Regionals Q14]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "I used a pipette and confirmed it myself",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #96 [2018 Monta Vista Tryouts Q1]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "27",
        "explanation": "The volume of is 10^21 meters and the weigh of water per cubic meter is 10^3 kg and kg to g is 10^3. Mutiply everything and we get 10^27",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "How tall is Mount Everest in meters?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "$5645, each $ has 100 pennies, so total is 5.645e3 * 1e2 which rounds up to an answer of 6",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #20": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "18",
        "explanation": "https://www.usgs.gov/faqs/how-much-natural-water-there#:~:text=Earth%20is%20estimated%20to%20hold,glaciers%20(fresh)%2024%2C064%2C000%20cubic%20kilometers",
        "credit": "Discord: errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #17 [2018 Westlake Q24]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "https://www.aar.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/AAR-Ohio-State-Fact-Sheet.pdf \n\nThe Association of American Railroads states in the above pdf that there's 5,139 miles of railroad tracks, so the answer would round up to 4. I hope I'm not coming off sounding mean; just want the info as accurate as possible  \ud83d\udc4d",
        "credit": "thatperson2647"
    },
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #30": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "16 Disney-owned movies were released in 2016; an average of 2 hours per movie moves around 97,000 seconds. Final answer is 5",
        "credit": "@tripleqgaming (discord)"
    },
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #27": {
        "question": "A particle is placed in a rigid box (the walls are impenetrable). What is the probability of finding it anywhere within (percent)? For reference, the one dimensional wave equation is \u03c8=Asin[(n\u03c0/L)*x]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Clarifying the problem because it's 2 as in 100%",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #41": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "Most sources (Statista, for instance) suggest that the average Japanese eats just under 100 pounds of rice per year. This is around a bowl of rice a day, if we were to make a reasonable guess during a test. The Japanese life expectancy also happens to be just under 100 (mid-80s). 10^2 * 10^2 produces a Fermi number of 4.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #133 [2019 Dartmouth Q16]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "100 pizzas * $10/pizza * 100 pennies/dollar = 10^5\n\nCJB",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #73 [2019 Northmont Q75]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "12 bacteria on 4 sq cm of skin",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (rafaelnadal) 17-18, #34": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "real answer would be n where 300*2^n=c",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "The average square foot of grass has 3,000 blades (https://www.quora.com/Has-anyone-ever-calculated-how-many-blades-of-grass-are-in-a-typical-lawn#:~:text=The%20average%20square%20foot%20of,Oklahoma%20Museum%20of%20Natural%20History%20.), so one foot likely contacts about a tenth of that area (average foot is 100 cm^2 = 0.1 ft^2), so about 300 blades are contacted",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #111 [2019 SOUP Q38]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "According to the Cleveland Clinic, humans breath around 12-18 times per minute. The average test taker could, using simple observation, presume a similar rate. There are around 5 * 10^5 minutes in a year. That's a range of 6-9 * 10^6, which provides a Fermi answer of 7. Even without this knowledge, an answer of 9 suggests around 30 breaths per second, with is plainly wrong up or down an order of magnitude.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #2": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "The enrollment in 2017-2018 was 5,260, meaning that the fermi number should be 4",
        "credit": "King Von"
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #18": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "12",
        "explanation": "log of [44^9 (characters expected for the monkeys to type out one \"GOOD SOUP\") divided by 400 characters per minute (100 wpm = 400 cpm)]",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #102 [2018 Princeton Q A39]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-5",
        "explanation": "Volume of a grain of rice is about 0.02 mL = 2e-5 L, so the fraction of the 2L bottle occupied is 1e-5",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #21": {
        "question": "How many primes are less than 10^100?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "greg"
    },
    "MIT Invitational 21-22, #36": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "27",
        "explanation": "Solar constant (flux) is about 1368 W/m^2 (note W = J/s), so energy captured in a minute is 60s * 1368 W/m^2 = 82000 J. Energy consumption of a 1600 lumen lightbulb is about 15 W, so the lightbulb stays on for 82000 J / 15 W = 5500 s. A jiffy is 3e-24 seconds, so converting to jiffies, the time is 1.8e27 jiffies, so the answer is 27.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "Your heart beats once per second at least, 1.5 e7 seconds in half of a year (six months)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #2": {
        "question": "How many NERDS ropes would it take to wrap around Mars?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "what does it mean \"in miles\" sir?????",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #12": {
        "question": "Find 3^33",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #18": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-11",
        "explanation": "K.E. = 1/2 m v^2 = 1/2 * 1.67 * 10^-27 * (1.5 * 10^8)^2 =",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #36": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "12",
        "explanation": "3*10^8 m/s * 60 s/minute * 36 inch/meter (also google)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "idk the intended question but hour per hour is really sussy",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Rickards SO Invitational 22-23, #42": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "5190 is not the fermi answer it is the normal answer",
        "credit": "Paresh"
    },
    "BirdSO Invitational 20-21, #17": {
        "question": "How many feathers equal the weight of the heaviest slug species?",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "Heaviest slug species (California slug) is 0.25 pounds, weight of a feather is 8.2 milligrams. 13,829 feathers equal the weight of a California slug)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Harvard Invitational 22-23, #4": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "38",
        "explanation": "2 mols released per tree per year, 12 trees, 2 + 12 + 24 = 38",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #53 [2018 Westlake Q27]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "1 General Sherman tree is 84 meters. Distance to the moon is 3.8e8m. Dividing gives 4.5e6 -> 6",
        "credit": "TheBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #38": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "16",
        "explanation": "whether using simple or compound interest, 1000(1.03)^1000 or 1000e^(1000*.03) gives 16",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "Volume of m&m is about 0.6 mL, available volume of car is about 2000 L (3000L before subtracting stuff like engine, seats, etc.), 2000L / (6e-4 L) = 3.33 million, so the answer is 6",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #41": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "the size n is not shown (unless this is intentional)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #2": {
        "question": "What is 7^45?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "caret not shown, the answer 38 thus makes no sense (745 -> 3)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #5": {
        "question": "The largest prime number discovered to date is 2^74,207,281 - 1. How many digits does this number have?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "missing caret and +1",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #3 [2018 Princeton Q B9]": {
        "question": "What is the number of cells in an adult male human body?",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "According to a new analysis of more than 1,500 papers, the average adult male human has around 36 trillion cells \u2014 that's 36 followed by 12 zeros \u2014 while adult females have 28 trillion and 10-year-old children have about 17 trillion.",
        "credit": "Troy Athens SciOly"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #13": {
        "question": "What fraction of the distance from the Earth to the Moon is this height? [Height of all the light bulbs sold in a year stacked together]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #42": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "16",
        "explanation": "google it lol",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #43": {
        "question": "How many iron atoms are on the tip of a safety pin (the pointy part)?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "typically the head of a pin refers to the round part",
        "credit": "P JAYA"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #125 [2018 Centerville Q18]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "I dont know if the fizz is right here, but if the answer is 5g=50->2, g is less than 10, so the answer should be 1.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #39": {
        "question": "How many ways are there to make change for $10?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #34 [2019 Captains Exchange: NCSSM Q15]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "30 pages rounds to 1???? either that or the question needs to be reworded",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "University of Michigan Invitational 17-18, #3": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-76",
        "explanation": "Method 1: Probability of each event and multiplying\n\nProbability of a tie: Since there are 3 options for each player and they need to match, the probability of a tie in one round is 1/3 * 1/3 = 1/9.\nProbability of 72 ties in a row: This is simply the probability of a tie happening on each round 72 times, so it's (1/9)^72.\nProbability of any non-tie outcome: Once we have 72 ties, the next round must break the tie and therefore not be a tie. This means the probability of any non-tie outcome is 1 - (probability of a tie) = 1 - 1/9 = 8/9.\nNow, we need to multiply the probability of getting 72 ties in a row followed by a non-tie outcome: (1/9)^72 * 8/9 \u2248 5.062 x 10^-76",
        "credit": "-sorryforthetypo"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #35 [2019 Solon Q9]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "bruv look it up",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #47": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "dump truck volume is 10 m^3 and grand canyon is like 4 * 10^12 m^2",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "Ohio State Invitational 22-23, #8": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "1 drop has the volume of 0.05ml, 1 olympic sized swimming pool contains 2.5e6 liters. 2.5e6/0.05e-3 gives 5e10 = 11",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #37": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "each grain of sand is -13 m^3, empire state building is 6m^3, so 19 grains are required",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #82 [2019 Captains Exchange: Irvine Q10]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "i mean it never specified front/back, 91 pages is 2",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #19": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "According to a new report, the average cost per inmate in New York's prisons is $167,731 per year.  - first google search",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #26 [2018 Aviation Q5]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "27",
        "explanation": "Volume of earth is 1e21m^3 = 1e27 mL, each skittle is about 0.5-1 mL, resulting in an answer of 1-2e27 skittles in the earth.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #105 [2019 Polytechnic Q24]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-9",
        "explanation": "probability of being struck in lifetime = 6.5e-5; if we assume that the probability of getting struck per day is x, then (1 - x) ^ (80 * 365 days) = 1 - 6.5e-5; solving gives x is around 2.2 * 10^-9",
        "credit": "Ryan PARK"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #60 [2019 Boca Raton Tryouts Q11]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "bro its not a hard problem lol",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #2": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "the original question did not ask how far it could write but how many pencils would it take so the assumption would be to take the length of the pencil which would be 18 cm and it would take approximetly 2 x 10^8 pencils to circle the earth",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #25": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "21",
        "explanation": "Volume of the Pacific Ocean is 7x10^20 liters. A soup can is 12 fluid ounces->0.35 liters. 7/0.35=20->2x10^21->21 cans needed to fill the Pacific Ocean",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #47": {
        "question": "How many hours would it take the world\u2019s fastest plane to fly the Earth's orbit?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #21": {
        "question": "How many newspapers would be needed put side-to-side to cover the surface of the Sun?",
        "answer": "Not sure, but it sure isn't 10",
        "explanation": "The surface area of the sun is 10^12 km, so unless a newspaper is kilometers long, this answer is wrong.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #36 [2019 Boca Raton Tryouts Q29]": {
        "question": "How much does Bill Gates\u2019 net worth weigh in 10 dollar bills? Express your answer in grams.",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "Gate's net worth is at a magnitude of 11, ten dollar bills make it ^10 bills, 1 bill is 1 gram.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #3": {
        "question": "What fraction (expressed as a decimal) of positive integers less than 10^100 are perfect squares?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "BTHS SciOly"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #5": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "8 people in germany, 2 liters per person",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #20": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "The Philippines is an archipelago that comprises 7,641 islands --> rounds up to 4.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #14": {
        "question": "How big is Duke\u2019s campus (including every part of Duke-owned land) according to Google in cm^2?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "How many meters tall would stacking all of these light bulbs be? [All the light bulbs sold in a year]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #12": {
        "question": "How many of the world's tallest building stacked on top of each other would reach this height? [Height of all the light bulbs sold in a year stacked together]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Carolina Invitational 22-23, #17": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "\"With good reason, the Swiss are the world\u2019s most enthusiastic rail users, traveling an average of 2,450 kilometers every year by train.\"\n\nhttps://www.cnn.com/travel/article/world-record-train-switzerland/index.html\n\nLikely the original answer was in regards to km, but the real answer should be in meters, like the question asks for...",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #39": {
        "question": "What is the volume of air breathed by the whole US population each month in liters?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Missing units...",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #116 [2019 Columbia Q3]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "37",
        "explanation": "4.2 million solar masses * 2e30 kg/solar mass = 8.4e36 kg, so the answer is 37",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #8": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "30 days * 24 hrs/day * 30 mm/hr = 21600",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #14": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-7",
        "explanation": "Thickness of paper is about 0.05-0.2 mm = 5-10 x 10^-5 m. A mile is 1609 meters, so thickness in miles is 5-20 x 10^-5 m x (1 mi / 1609 m) = 3.11-12.43 e-8 mi. Different sources give different numbers for thickness of paper ranging from 0.05-0.1 mm all the way up to 9 mil (~0.2 mm), so probably the safest answer here is -7.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #38": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "68",
        "explanation": "bro whoever made this test is incompetent",
        "credit": "Craig B"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2018 Westlake Q44]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "There are 6e18 electrons in a coulomb. Given that wattage is equal to amperage times voltage, at a standard US voltage of 120, that means there's half an amp running through a 60 watt bulb. 6e18 electrons divided by 0.5 amps is a 1.2e19. Likewise, if we use a more global voltage of 240 volts, that would mean a quarter of an amp is running through a 60 watt bulb. 6e18 electrons divided by 0.25 amps is 2.4e19, which would also be 19. Not sure why the original answer was negative.",
        "credit": "cubicfrog (disc)"
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #3": {
        "question": "How many dead skin cells are shed by all the people on Earth each year?",
        "answer": "20",
        "explanation": "40,000 per minute, 525,000 minutes in a year, 8 bil people in the world --> 1.68*e20",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #1 [2018 Westlake Q64]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-23",
        "explanation": "Mass of earth is 6*10^24 kg, average mass of man is 80 kg -> 80/(6*10^24) = 1.3*10^-23, answer is -23",
        "credit": "bibob"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #19": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "10^6 liters in an olympic swimming pool, ~5 balls in a liter, 10^7 balls total",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 23-24, #9": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "5 is a fibonacci number for which F_n/F_n-1 is within 5% of phi. The percent error for 5/3 compared to phi is surprisingly low at only ~3%, so the answer to the question is 1.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #114 [2019 Solon Q10]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "google the thickness ur tweaking",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #53": {
        "question": "The n-th Fermat number is defined as F_n = 2^(2^n) + 1. What is log(F_2023)? Here log denotes the base-10 logarithm.",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "bibob/pikapika007"
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #49": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "10 electrons per molecule of water (2*1 + 8), each mole of water has N_A = 6.022*10^23 molecules of water, final answer is 6*10^24 which is 25",
        "credit": "bibob/pikapika007"
    },
    "Centerville Invitational 17-18, #26": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "20*12*2= 480 m^3, 480*1000*1000 = 4.8e8 ml, 1 drop of water is 0.05 mL, 4.8e8/0.05 = 9.6e9 which rounds to 10.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "The number of digits is 10^1.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #102 [2019 Duke Q5]": {
        "question": "What is the density at the center of the Sun (in grams per centimeter cubed)?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Include units of density that should be used.",
        "credit": "chez_republic1052, alphalion0205"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #4": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "151",
        "explanation": "log 2 = 0.301 -> 0.301*500=150.5, which rounds up to 151",
        "credit": "dc"
    },
    "Rickards Invitational 23-24, #45": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "not sure what the answer is but if theres only 19 grains of sand on earth there cant be 24 in the sahara",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #44": {
        "question": "Assuming a Bluetooth 4 connection, how many Airpod earbuds would you need to cover the entire Earth?",
        "answer": "18",
        "explanation": "surface area of earth : 4pi r^2 : e1 * e7 * e7 m = e15 m^2 \n\ne3 buds / sq meter? \n\napprox e18",
        "credit": "me"
    },
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #22": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "0",
        "explanation": "Amount of dirt per swimming pool: 1.5g/cm^3 dirt * (10000 cm^3 per cubic meter) * (50 * 25 *2 meters^3) * (1kg/1000g) = 3750 kg\n\nWeight of an adult blue whale: ~110,000 kg\n\nPools per whale: ~29 (1)",
        "credit": "Trippy (@tripleqgaming for discord)"
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #14": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "distance from earth to sun is at least 10^11 meters, cannot be less than 11",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Palo Alto Tryouts 22-23, #31": {
        "question": "How many different books have been published in the world?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "The fermi answer 8 is given as the number of published books in the world, not the total copies of books in the world.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "Text is probably a typo and the Q should be revised, but 41,124 is 4.1124*10^4 or 4.",
        "credit": "Trippy (@tripleqgaming on Discord)"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 22-23, #12": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-5",
        "explanation": "if its a ratio of revolutionary to ww1 thats R/W which should be negative",
        "credit": "Him"
    },
    "BirdSO Invitational 20-21, #40": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-48",
        "explanation": "(1/3)^100 is 1.9e-48",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #77 [2019 Cornell Q28]": {
        "question": "How many liters of gasoline does the average american use in their lifetime",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "nom nom gasoline",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UMass Amherst Invitational 22-23, #34": {
        "question": "Jalal flips an unfair coin (heads 3 10 of the time and tails 7 10 of the time) 50 times and calls it an experiment. On average, how many experiments will Jalal have to conduct until he flips at least 48 tails in one experiment?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #11": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "Speed of S waves is 1-8 km/s (for our purposes we will take the average and go 4 km/s), san francisco to syracuse is 4000 km (3926 km but close enough), 4000/4 = 1000 seconds = 1*10^6 ms which is 6",
        "credit": "bibob/pikapika007"
    },
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #12": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "google says 3 x 10^19",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "University of Georgia Invitational 23-24, #2": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "48",
        "explanation": "moon volume is 2e25 mL, which is 1.2e24 moles of water, which is 7.4e47 molecules, which is 1.5e48 hydrogen atoms",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #25": {
        "question": "What is the volume of a golf ball measured in cubic hectometers?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Carolina Invitational 22-23, #30": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "602051",
        "explanation": "WolframAlpha gives CatalanNumber[1000000] = 5.5*10^602051.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #2": {
        "question": "How many carbon atoms fit from the distance from sea level to the highest point on earth?",
        "answer": "14",
        "explanation": "everest 8800m = e4 m \ncarbon atom 1 angstrom = e-10m \n\n14 m ?",
        "credit": "evanescent"
    },
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #34": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "3",
        "explanation": "1 atm ~= 760mmHg which is 3",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #96 [2018 Monta Vista Tryouts Q15]": {
        "question": "How many small calories does the sun output per second?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "the sun outputs 26 watts so for the answer to be 26 it would need to be small calories which can be ambiguous",
        "credit": ""
    }
}
corrections_list = [
    "UT Austin Invitational 18-19, #22",
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #5",
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "UT Austin Invitational 17-18, #19",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #25",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #6",
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #43",
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #13",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #6",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #18 [2018 Brown Q19]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #75 [2019 Polytechnic Q19]",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #1",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #11 [2019 Eastside / Haslett Q14]",
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2019 LISO Q14]",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #15",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #66 [2019 Northmont Q5]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #7",
    "Princeton Invitational 22-23, #33",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #22",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #34",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #16",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #26",
    "UT Austin Invitational 18-19, #13",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 22-23, #1",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #16",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #16",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #11",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #18",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #11",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #16 [2018 Harvard Q4]",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #7",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #21",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #37",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #45",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #39",
    "UT Austin Invitational 22-23, #17",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #31",
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #10",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #12",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #98 [2019 ATX Regionals Q41]",
    "University of Michigan Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #32",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2019 WWPN Q3]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #32",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #1",
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "SSSS Fermi (randomsci) 22-23, #23",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #3",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #21",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #40",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #67 [2018 WWPN Tryouts Q1]",
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #10",
    "UT Austin Invitational 17-18, #21",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #85 [2018 U Georgia Q2]",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #16",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #131 [2019 New Trier Q10]",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #5",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #14",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #3",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #36",
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #60",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #27",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #6",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #1",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #33 [2018 Westlake Q47]",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #31",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #33",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #10",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #31",
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #7",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #110 [2019 Monta Vista Q22]",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #12",
    "SSSS Fermi (randomsci) 22-23, #27",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 22-23, #38",
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #49",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #22",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #19",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #1",
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #11",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #7",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #41",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #6 [2019 Virginia Tech Q4]",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #11",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #22 [2018 Acton-Box Q15]",
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #46",
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #1",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #80 [2019 U Chicago Q21]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #109 [2018 U Florida Regionals Q14]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #96 [2018 Monta Vista Tryouts Q1]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #41",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5",
    "SSSS Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #20",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #17 [2018 Westlake Q24]",
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #30",
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #27",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #41",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #133 [2019 Dartmouth Q16]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #73 [2019 Northmont Q75]",
    "SSSs Fermi (rafaelnadal) 17-18, #34",
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #111 [2019 SOUP Q38]",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #41",
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #2",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #18",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #102 [2018 Princeton Q A39]",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #21",
    "MIT Invitational 21-22, #36",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #21",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #2",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #12",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #18",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #36",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #21",
    "Rickards SO Invitational 22-23, #42",
    "BirdSO Invitational 20-21, #17",
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #2",
    "Harvard Invitational 22-23, #4",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #53 [2018 Westlake Q27]",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #38",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #24",
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #41",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #2",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #5",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #3 [2018 Princeton Q B9]",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #13",
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #42",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #43",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #125 [2018 Centerville Q18]",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #39",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #34 [2019 Captains Exchange: NCSSM Q15]",
    "University of Michigan Invitational 17-18, #3",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #35 [2019 Solon Q9]",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #47",
    "Ohio State Invitational 22-23, #8",
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #37",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #82 [2019 Captains Exchange: Irvine Q10]",
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #19",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #26 [2018 Aviation Q5]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #105 [2019 Polytechnic Q24]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #60 [2019 Boca Raton Tryouts Q11]",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #2",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #25",
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #47",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #21",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #36 [2019 Boca Raton Tryouts Q29]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #53 [2018 Westlake Q27]",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #3",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #13",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #5",
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #20",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #14",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #12",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #13",
    "Carolina Invitational 22-23, #17",
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #39",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #116 [2019 Columbia Q3]",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #8",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #14",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #10",
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #38",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2018 Westlake Q44]",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #3",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #1 [2018 Westlake Q64]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #19",
    "UT Austin Invitational 23-24, #9",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #114 [2019 Solon Q10]",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #53",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #49",
    "Centerville Invitational 17-18, #26",
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #102 [2019 Duke Q5]",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #4",
    "Rickards Invitational 23-24, #45",
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #44",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #2",
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #22",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #14",
    "Palo Alto Tryouts 22-23, #31",
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "Princeton Invitational 22-23, #12",
    "BirdSO Invitational 20-21, #40",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #77 [2019 Cornell Q28]",
    "UMass Amherst Invitational 22-23, #34",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #11",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #12",
    "University of Georgia Invitational 23-24, #2",
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #25",
    "Carolina Invitational 22-23, #30",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #12",
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #2",
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #34",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #96 [2018 Monta Vista Tryouts Q15]"
]